13.
No light.
No door.
No sign.
Same face.
New line.
Still quiet.
Still mine.
Out to eat
I used to hide
behind the menu,
behind the glass.
My turn comes.
I look up fast.
"Spicy rigatoni.
"
That's it.
I asked.
---
13.
Small jump.
Not brave.
Just enough.
Still weird.
Still me.
Less scared
to be seen.
---
Grocery store.
Leave the cart.
One aisle over.
Beating heart.
Grab the thing.
Walk back smart.
No one knows.
I do.
That's the part.
---
13.
Small jump.
Not brave.
Just enough.
Still weird.
Still me.
Less scared
to be seen.
---
Teacher asks.
No one speaks.
Hints keep coming.
Room feels weak.
I know it.
Raise my hand.
Say the thing.
Room can breathe again.
---
Tomato sauce.
Tomato paste.
Cream in the pan.
Nothing to waste.
No seasoning.
No disguise.
I know enough
when I decide.
---
13.
Small jump.
Not brave.
Just enough.
I order.
I answer.
I leave.
I come back.
Still weird.
Still me.
Less hidden.
Less scared.