The clock on the wall has secrets we can't
speak,
Its hands are misplaced, its numbers
antique.
We glance at the ceiling, we stare at the
floor,
Time’s just a rumor we heard once before.
If no one can read it, does the second
even hit?
We’re checking our screens like they’re
telling us truth.
Maybe time’s just a game that we can’t
really quit,
And we’re lost in the halls, just trying
to fit.
The classroom’s a forest, and clocks are
the trees,
They fall every second, but no one
believes.
We borrow the time from a digital friend,
But what if the moments have no start or
end?
If no one can read it, does the second
even hit?
We’re checking our screens like they’re
telling us truth.
Maybe time’s just a game that we can’t
really quit,
And we’re lost in the halls, just trying
to fit.
So we stare at the ticking of clocks we
can’t know,
We’re never too early, we’re never too
slow.
The past is a myth and the future’s a
haze,
We’re stuck in this infinite maze.
If no one can read it, does the second
even hit?
We’re checking our screens like they’re
telling us truth.
Maybe time’s just a game that we can’t
really quit,
And we’re lost in the halls, just trying
to fit.