(Verse 1 – Alarm One)
Alarm goes off, six-thirty-two,
Mom at the door like she always do.
Everything’s fog, ceiling spins,
Then I smile when it sinks in.
It’s just the first one, false alarm,
Still got time, no cause for harm.
World can wait, dreams still hot,
I sink back down into brain rot.
(Verse 2 – Alarm Two)
Alarm again, different tone,
Mom says, “Up,” I half-way groan.
Eyes open now, room comes back,
I scan the floor, my hoodie rack.
Think about school, what day it is,
Sweats or sweats, don’t know which.
Start a plan, then lose the plot,
Slip right back into brain rot.
(Verse 3 – Alarm Three)
Alarm explodes, Mom’s not calm,
Standing there with folded arms.
“This isn’t confusion, it’s a choice”, she
said
Weaponized incompetence ringing in my head
Brain snaps on, stomach drops,
Latin test, declensions, clocks.
I sit straight up, fog gets shot,
No more room for brain rot.
Three alarms to be a person,
Mind too soft, attention cursin’.
Morning steals what sleep forgot,
I wake up fighting brain rot.