Mustard chicken, hambāgu, then fajita
night
Cedar plank salmon when the timing’s right
It’s meatloaf, corn chowder, curry, then
dip
Mom’s dinner rotation never skips
Dad takes a bite, then tests the claim
My sister fires back — it’s always the
same
I lean back on two chair legs, don’t make
a sound
I like to watch while they go round
Pronouns: he/she/they/vio
“Did you see the TikTok on Sora though?”
Columbia protests, Elon’s afraid
Ozempic’s $550 a day
Hot girl pills, NPR race stats
Anne Frank memes, “You can’t say that”
Can you land a plane? Dad says “maybe”
Sister says “That’s peak Dad crazy”
Mustard chicken, hambāgu, then fajita
night
Cedar plank salmon when the timing’s right
It’s meatloaf, corn chowder, curry, then
dip
Mom’s dinner rotation never skips
Dad takes a bite, then questions the frame
My sister rolls eyes — it’s part of the
game
I lean back on two chair legs, don’t make
a sound
I like to watch while they go round
Chick-fil-A Sundays, OG offensive
Apple rules in the Dutch defensive
Dad says causation ain’t correlation
Sister groans, says “Colonization”
Dad says baking’s not his thing
Sister says “You just fear measuring”
Dad shrugs. “Exactly.” She shouts “Proof!”
Then asks if seals can hear sonic booms
BLTs, quesadillas, ham rolls warm
Katsu on Thursdays if there’s a storm
Yearly theme, vaccine clause
Truman Show logic, Elon flaws
“Netflix is cringe,” “Swift says ‘swear’”
“K-pop fans staged a digital war”
“Math is down,” “Haircuts cost”
“I choose the bear,” I say — then I’m lost
---
Mustard chicken, hambāgu, then fajita
night
Cedar plank salmon when the timing’s right
It’s French dip, avgolemono, and dumpling
stew
The rotation always cycles through
Dad takes a bite, says “That’s not the
cause”
Sister brings Marx, Dad counters with laws
I lean back on two chair legs, don’t make
a sound
I like to watch while they go round