Walked into Carmel, Indiana heat,
Poke in the back, sugar at my feet.
Kiosk said choose — I said "yes to it
all,"
From tapioca pearls to the weird jelly
ball.
Strawberry, lychee, grass jelly flood,
Red bean sinking like a snack in mud.
Crystal, mango, yogurt surprise,
Kiwi's popping like fire in my eyes.
Twenty-five bucks for a cup so wild,
Texture roulette, like a bouncy child.
Carmel’s finest, chaos in a straw,
A sugar-loaded ride, no rules at all.
Matcha milk foam, blueberry burst,
Peach on top just to make it worse.
Every topping stacked like a dare,
Sip once, now you’re stuck in there.
They ask if I want less ice — nah, full
send,
This drink’s not a vibe, it’s a lifelong
friend.
Sinking in pearls, rising in dreams,
Caffeinated joy, sugar-laced screams.
Twenty-five bucks and a laugh too loud,
Couch in the corner, cup tall and proud.
Dad spots one dirty table,
starts preaching aloud —
“Attention,” he says, “is all that it
takes.”
Like that AI paper, but with bobba and
takes.