We said next July,
same lake, same week,
same bags on the bunks,
same dumb no-sleep.
Same camp map,
same mess hall line,
same names on the list,
just not this time.
You said, “I’m still me,”
I said, “I know,”
but the form says girl,
and the answer’s no.
So the same old place
where we always went
is still taking girls,
but the girls all went.
You were my friend,
and you’re my friend,
and he’s my friend
who was she back then.
And I know that’s wrong,
or the wrong way round,
but my mouth gets lost
where my thoughts get found.
If she’s he and he’s still you,
and you’re still you but the rule says
“who,”
how’s a girls’ camp a girls’ camp
when the girls aren’t there?
If we said we’d go like we always do,
and I still mean me and I still mean you,
why’s the same same place
suddenly somewhere?
I can still see us
by the dock at dusk,
trading ghost stories,
trading clothes for luck.
You in that hoodie,
her in that hat,
him in the photo
before all that.
Or after that.
Or during. Wait.
Was that before
you changed your name?
I know your face.
I knew your face.
I know it now
in a different way.
They said, “It’s simple.”
I said, “It’s not.”
They said, “Just love them.”
I said, “I do.”
But love’s not the part
that I’m tripping through.
It’s camp in June
and the missing you.
If she’s he and he’s still you,
and you’re still you but the rule says
“who,”
how’s a girls’ camp a girls’ camp
when the girls aren’t there?
If we said we’d go like we always do,
and I still mean me and I still mean you,
why’s the same same place
suddenly somewhere?
They can’t come in
because they’re boys now.
I can go back,
but not with them now.
And that’s the part
that no one says plain,
how change can fit
and still rearrange.
So I can get it
and still feel weird.
I can be kind
and still want last year.
I can say “him”
and still miss “her,”
not who he is,
just when we were.
If she’s he and he’s still you,
and you’re still you and I know that’s
true,
why does truth make room
and take room too?
If we’re still friends,
and I know we are,
why’s the bunk feel full
and the whole camp far?
If summer comes
and the forms stay same,
can I miss the camp
and still say your name?
I still know you.
I still do.
I just don’t know
what summer does
with that truth.