Said I was gluten-free last fall at school
Now I pack my snacks and follow the rule
My friends all nod like they understand
I pass on the pizza and play it bland
Pretending’s easy once you’ve begun
They bring me rice cakes by the ton
I fake a frown, but truth be said—
I kinda like the gluten-free bread
No one asked, I just went along
Now it’s quinoa chips and chickpea song
I miss the wheat, but not with dread
‘Cause I kinda like the gluten-free bread
I dodge the bread line with quiet grace
Skip every crust, keep a straight face
It’s spongy, crumbly, not the best—
But I’m still not unimpressed
I never meant to lie, not deep
Just wanted in, a tribe to keep
Now flaxseed wraps are in my head
And I kinda like the gluten-free bread
No one asked, I just went along…