Name on a screen.
High-res. Still fake.
Everyone certain.
I'm buffering.
Used to win
off the bounce.
Now it's
figure it out.
Guards down.
No assist.
Left or right,
can't pick.
If it misses,
it's legit.
We check the screen
like it's truth.
No undo.
I choose.
Da says
"this could be big."
I miss.
He says "maybe not"
Big future
I don't feel.
Just trying
something real.
Guards down.
No assist.
Left or right,
can't pick.
If it misses,
it's legit.
We check the screen
like it's truth.
No undo.
I choose.
No rails.
No save.
No soft
version of brave.
Pick a side.
Live with it.
Half wrong
still counts as it.
Guards down.
Say it clean.
No in-between.
Left or right,
still pick.
Miss or hit,
it sticks.
No edits.
No tricks.
Guards down.
I stay.
Not there.
Still play.