Verse 1:
Saw a woman bake a cake with one good hand
A man proposed with a marching band
There’s a kid who cries when his dog gets
found
And a girl who cuts her hair, just lets it
fall down
Verse 2:
I’ve never left this little room
But I’ve been to Paris and a honeymoon
I know heartbreak on a subway ride
And how to smile when your father dies
Chorus:
I learned it all in fifteen seconds
Swipe away before the pain sets in
Every story’s got a filter on
Still I cried when the soldier came home
Verse 3:
I keep a charger by my bed
Like a Bible for the walking dead
Truth’s a flash and then it’s gone
But I write my songs like I was there all
along
Chorus:
I learned it all in fifteen seconds
Played pretend ‘til it felt like lessons
A world of strangers in my phone
But I’ve lived a thousand lives alone