The bearing of bearing, the difference of
strain
The importance of noticing, again and
again
Bearing the burden, bearing the glare
The difference between silence and care
Difference makes difference, it multiplies
slow
Bearing what’s buried, the importance will
grow
Bearing the past, bearing the stare
The difference is real when the witness is
there
Importance of bearing, of bearing
difference
Difference in presence, in patience, in
penance
Bearing importance, importance of voice
Bearing the difference, the hard and the
choice
Importance repeated, difference unshaken
Bearing the blame that was never forsaken
Bearing the hurt, bearing the slight
Difference held steady still shines a
light
Bear the bearing, bear the break
Difference makes the silence quake
Importance isn’t once or twice—
It’s every bearing, every price
The importance. The bearing. The
difference we hold.
The bearing. The difference. The stories
retold.
The difference. The bearing. The
importance that stays.
More difference. More bearing. More honest
days.