Everybody needs a second room
A place to hide, a place to bloom
Mom has one, but don’t say where
It’s secret like next week’s dinner fare
My sister has a second too
A style quite different, it’s red, not
blue
She calls it home, the Rat Palace lives
With hammocks, tubes, and snacks she gives
One year we made the space for mine
Cleared out Dad’s old Zoom call shrine
He’s got a second house, it’s fair
So now I’ve got four walls and air
My second room has no light switch
Just a glow I didn’t pick
Overhead, it hums too bright
It stays on day and night
It must mean something — I can’t say which
But my second room has no light switch
I placed some screens from old Japan
They fold like waves, they stand, not hang
A mountain scene, a paper crane
A wall that doesn’t quite explain
There’s no bed, just a desk and chair
A chalkboard waits with chalk to spare
No clicks, no off, just quiet beams
And maybe that’s what silence means
My second room has no light switch
Just a truth you learn but can’t quite fix
Overhead, the quiet burn
Like someone left it on, forgot to return
It feels like something soft and stitched
In my second room with no light switch
One day I might ask why that is
Or maybe I won’t — it just exists
Some things you live with, some you ditch
Like my second room with no light switch