Moved south.
Less said.
Sky wide.
In my head.
Tiny house.
One light.
Wi-Fi on.
All night.
No mortgage.
That’s it.
No rent.
No split.
Big land.
No one near.
Cheap dirt.
Still here.
Ramen run.
Once a week.
Don’t need much.
Don’t speak.
Neighbors?
Miles out.
Signal full.
No doubt.
Day burns.
Same view.
Time slips.
Nothing new.
No mortgage.
That’s it.
No rent.
No split.
Big land.
No one near.
Cheap dirt.
Still here.
Ramen run.
Once a week.
Don’t need much.
Don’t speak.
They ask
why I left.
I say
nothing left.
Full bars.
Still mute.
I see you.
Just don’t.
No mortgage.
Say it slow.
No boss.
Nowhere to go.
Just land.
Just sky.
Low cost.
Still high.
Ramen run.
That’s the plan.
Tiny house.
Big land.