Didn’t stretch, didn’t warm up much
Held the racket like a coffee cup
Coach said try to find your spell
Just breathe and swing and hope it fell
Underhand serve, yeah that’s my call
Not fast, not tricky — but it beats them
all
They swing too wild or let it go
I win the point just keeping it low
School van hums as we head out
No one cheers, but we don’t doubt
Somewhere out there, we pretend to hear
A quiet roar from Brooks the Bear
Mostly we walk around picking up balls
Crocs squeak loud in the quiet of it all
No crowd, no stats on a wall
Just one more serve, Crocs and all
Coach says I’m the most chill on the team
Even when it’s match point, I don’t scream
I just stand there, take my time
Hit it in and everything’s fine
Mostly we walk around picking up balls
Lose track of score, forget who falls
I’m not great — but I don’t stall
Second serve, Crocs and all
Parents wait in the lot, quiet and kind
Wave as we wander off the backline
It’s not for glory, not for a call
We just keep showing up — Crocs and all