Had a little girl’s bed made of pine
Slide on the side and a ladder to climb
Underneath was a temple space
Where I’d sit for hours in a quiet place
One day I stood there, legs too long
The steps felt short, the fit felt wrong
Stopped climbing up, just stayed below
Then took to the couch like it was my own
Crashed in the middle of the downstairs
floor
Blankets piled, shoes by the door
Everyone stepping around my spot
They did complain — but not a lot
Some things change without much plan
You don’t outgrow — you just expand
It looks like a sofa, but it’s a bed they
say
With a trundle drawer for friends to stay
Dad took weeks to list but sold real fast
We hauled it out the door and the memories
passed
A lady pulled up the driveway with care
And the slide went rolling through the air
By then I’d claimed the couch as mine
Back was sore but I said I was fine
Mom said, “Let’s fix this couch-bed thing”
Found me a frame with a curving wing
Some things change without much plan
You don’t outgrow — you just expand
It looks like a sofa, but it’s a bed they
say
With a trundle drawer for friends to stay
Got some throw pillows, velvet and bright
With beads and tassels and gold stitched
light
They’re kind of a lot — a little too much
But I love how they sparkle when I touch
Some things change without much sound
Just a slide bed gone and a new one found
It looks like a sofa, but it’s a bed they
say
With a trundle drawer for friends to stay