Out in front. Didn’t run.
Got there first just for fun.
Everyone tries to pass.
I don’t move. Make it last.
Slow walk. Set the pace.
What’s the rush to the same place?
If time’s real, let it prove.
I don’t chase. I let it move.
They go fast. Call it drive.
I go slow. Still arrive.
Eyes on me like I’m wrong.
But I’ve been here this long.
Slow walk. Set the pace.
What’s the rush to the same place?
If time’s real, let it prove.
I don’t chase. I let it move.
If I’m late, who decides?
Clocks just talk. I don’t buy.
If I stop, nothing breaks.
World keeps up. That’s the play.
Slow walk. Say it twice.
I don’t speed to feel alive.
If it comes, then it’s mine.
If it doesn’t, still fine.
Slow walk. Front of line.
No one knows what is time.