[Chorus]
The importance of bearing witness—
To show you saw, to say you knew.
To hold the silence, speak the truth,
Even when the wind blows cruel.
The importance of bearing witness.
[Verse 1]
To watch and not look away,
To say, “I was there,”
To hold a story that’s not your own
Like it matters that you care.
To see the cracks and name them plain,
To know it’s not just someone else’s pain.
[Chorus]
Bearing witness—it matters so.
Like rain that helps the wildflowers grow.
A record kept in soul, not stone,
So no one has to stand alone.
Bearing witness—it matters so.
[Verse 2]
To listen when it’s hard to hear,
To sit with truth, even smeared in fear.
To lift a voice that’s growing faint,
To stand, not as a saint,
But as someone who chose to stay.
Just stayed. And heard. And didn’t look
away.
[Chorus]
The importance of bearing witness—
To echo cries that fade too fast.
To make a moment hold and last,
To be the mirror, not the mask.
The importance of bearing witness.
[Verse 3]
To carry weight that’s not your own,
To say, “I saw what had been shown.”
Not to fix, or shine, or save—
Just to walk beside the brave.
To show the wound, not just the scar.
To say, “I know who you are.”
[Chorus]
Bearing witness, it’s a vow—
To mark the then, to name the now.
So future hands can hold the thread,
Of what was done, what should be said.
Bearing witness, it’s a vow.
[Outro]
A whisper in the dark, a light dim but
true—
A thread between the me and you.
Stories caught and passed like flame,
So no one ever forgets the name.
That’s the importance of bearing witness.