I walk the house with just one in
The other sleeps in its plastic bin
Left ear takes the morning shift
Right comes in when spirits lift
With one AirPod, I can go all night long
Swapping sides like nothing’s wrong
Mono sound, a half-full song
But the vibe rolls steady, all night long
No surround, no perfect bass
But I stay in the rhythm race
Don’t need both to feel the beat
One’s enough to move my feet
With one AirPod, I can go all night long
Keep one charging while I hum along
Not stereo, not crystal-clear
But I’ve got sound in at least one ear
Battery low? That’s not my fate
I alternate and circulate
It’s not ideal, but it’s my way
To keep the music night and day
With one AirPod, I can go all night long
It’s not loud, but the will is strong
One side silent, one side plays—
And that’s how I stretch out all my days