Life on replay, learned it all online,
Like and subscribe, but you won’t own my
mind.
Raw and unfiltered, fame took a shot,
Digital kid, but I can’t be bought.
Got Crocs on stage; a bright-lit room,
I bear witness to tilt and the dinner
gloom.
Pillows too puffy, silence too loud,
Tuned my strings while avoiding the crowd.
[electric violin]
Twelve dollars a week, one tucked in my
sleeve,
Spend eleven on stuff I don’t really need.
Still got my grip, still seeing it
through,
Famous from birth, my name is Lily Roo.
Still ride with the carpool crowd,
Hop out early, skip the paint, stay proud.
Dad’s van smells good but don’t play the
part—
Gifts from the neighbor feel oddly like
art.
Still clean my room, still pack my food,
No gold-leaf mirror can shift my mood.
They say I shine—well maybe I do,
But I still take the trash out too.
Twelve dollars a week, one tucked in my
sleeve,
Spend eleven on stuff I don’t really need.
Still got my grip, still seeing it
through,
Famous from birth, my name is Lily Roo.
They’re pulling me towards neon dreams,
But home is a room where lights never
leave.
Bright enough already, no need for your
spark,
My stage, my rules, I thrive in the dark.
Born into whispers, raised to shout,
Never buying in, won’t sell out.
Twelve bucks weekly keeps me clear,
Bearing witness, why I’m here.