Room full of noise, hands in the air,
Everybody racing to get somewhere.
I’m in the back, clicking a fidget cube,
Watching the whole thing come unglued.
They say I’m quiet, they say I wait,
Like I’m late to some invisible gate.
But I’m just listening, stacking the
truth,
Letting it age, letting it proof.
I don’t burn words just to fill the air,
I don’t spend them like I don’t care.
When Lily talks, the room goes still,
Chairs stop scraping, even the ticking
chills.
I don’t say much, but when I do,
Every head nods like they always knew.
When Lily talks, you hear it twice,
Once in the sound, once in the silence.
Teachers say, “her voice matters,”
Friends listen close when she speaks, not
scattered.
I take my time, I read the room,
I don’t rush daylight, I don’t chase noon.
I work alone, I work just fine,
I’ll ask for help when the question’s
mine.
I don’t raise hands just to be seen,
I speak when the thought is sharp and
clean.
When Lily talks, people lean in,
Like they missed the start and this is the
win.
Not loud, not fast, not dressed to
impress,
Just one clear sentence, nothing less.
Attention isn’t noise or size,
It’s knowing when to open your mouth and
why.
You can shout all day, you can sell the
room,
But still miss the moment that lands the
boom.
When Lily talks, the room remembers,
Lunchroom, classroom, late November.
I don’t chase echoes, I don’t pursue,
I talk when it’s true — and then it’s
true.
I’ve been listening the whole damn time.