*(Verse 1)*
Busted out the screen door, sun was
sinking low,
Two little plants in busted pots, nowhere
else to go.
William’s leaves went yellow like a
roadside sign,
That’s how he says, “I’m thirsty,” and I
say, “Fine.”
*(Verse 2)*
He’s got that bonsai patience, quiet kind
of grace,
Never begs for water, just holds his
place.
I got a bottle of food, says “Use once a
week,”
But we don’t do rules, we don’t really
speak.
*(Chorus)*
Feelin’ free and easy with Dander near my
knee,
Named him after Davinder, but he flakes
you see.
Curled up leaves like pages in the wind,
Just me and the green things I never quite
tend.
*(Verse 3)*
Dander leans like he’s got a story to
tell,
Crooked but proud in that terra-cotta
shell.
We’ve seen cold nights and windows freeze,
But they stuck around like old melodies.
*(Chorus)*
Feelin’ free and easy with Dander near my
knee,
Named him after Davinder but it’s dandruff
you see.
William’s going gold, that’s my cue,
Two plants and a window and not much to
do.
*(Bridge)*
Could’ve read the label, could’ve tried
real hard,
But they like the mess — water rings and
disregard.
No mist, no feeding, just room to be,
And I swear those plants still believe in
me.
*(Final Chorus)*
Freedom’s just a quiet room with filtered
afternoon,
William looking noble, Dander out of tune.
Life rolls on, but I know what’s true
Two pots of patience, and me just passing
through.