Yeah, I can play the violin.
Took lessons from time to time, but they
weren’t required.
I mostly learned from a screen.
I’m chill, not wired.
I don’t need music, I don’t need rules.
I play what aches. I play what’s cool.
Mom tunes the strings when they fall out
of line—
But what I play? That mess is mine.
My first violin was cardboard.
Didn’t stop me from making sound.
I put it under my chin, then took a bow,
Let the rhythm spin me ‘round.
I don’t need music, I don’t need rules.
I play what aches. I play what’s cool.
Mom tunes the strings when they fall out
of line—
But what I play? That mess is mine.
I practice from the couch, no concerns at
all,
But only perform in a concert hall.
My bow’s a wand when the lights go dim—
I don’t play notes. I play what’s within.
I don’t need music, I don’t need rules.
I play what aches. I play what’s cool.
Mom tunes the strings when they fall out
of line—
But what I play? That mess is mine.